bestofferbuy.com 2010-06-26

# Privacy Notice : BestOfferBuy.com, Buy DVD, Shop for PC accessories, Discount MP3 Players, Bargain Deal for Surveillance Equipment, Cheap R4 for NDS, X-sim Unlock

BestOfferBuy.com respects your privacy. We will only collect, store and use your personal information for defined purposes. We use your information to support and enhance our relationship with you, for example, to process your purchase, provide service and support, and share product, service and company news and offerings with you. We safeguard and protect against unauthorized access, use and disclosure of your information by using appropriate measures and processes to maintain security. We do not sell your personal information. We only share your personal data with our other organization with your consent, as required by law or to protect BestOfferBuy.com, its customers, or the public, or with companies that help BestOfferBuy.com fulfill its obligations with you, and then only with partners who share BestOfferBuy.com's commitment to protecting your privacy and data. At any time you may contact BestOfferBuy.com with any privacy questions or concerns you may have. You also may ask at any time to see the personal data you have given us and request correction or deletion. We strive to protect the security of your personal data by use of appropriate measures and processes. 

**Privacy and Data Security**

At BestOfferBuy.com, your right to privacy and data security is a primary concern. That's why, when you visit BestOfferBuy.com, we help you maintain control over your personal data on the Internet. Below are the guidelines we use for protecting the information you provide us during a visit to our Internet sites ([www.BestOfferBuy.com](http://www.bestofferbuy.com/)) or when you use our online support offerings.

 **BestOfferBuy.com only asks for specific types of personal information**

In a few areas on our Web site and online customer support tools, we ask you to provide information that will enable us to enhance your site visit, to assist you with purchase and technical support issues or to follow up with you after your visit. It is completely optional for you to participate.

For example, we request information from you when you:

1\. Register on BestOfferBuy.com  
2\. Request a quote  
3\. Place an order  
4\. Provide feedback in an online survey  
5\. Subscribe to a newsletter or a mailing list  
6\. Contact us

Information we may request includes your name, e-mail address, phone number, address, type of business, credit card details, customer preference, experience, demographic and interest information, customer number and RMA number, as well as other similar personal information. If we ever ask for significantly different information we will inform you.

 **BestOfferBuy.com only uses your personal information for specific purposes**

The information you provide will be kept confidential and used to support your customer relationship with BestOfferBuy.com. Among other things, we want to help you quickly find information on BestOfferBuy.com and alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new products and services from BestOfferBuy.com. BestOfferBuy.com may enhance or merge your information collected at its site with data from third parties for purposes of marketing products or services to you.

In addition, BestOfferBuy.com may be required to disclose personal information in connection with law enforcement, fraud prevention, regulation, and other legal action or if BestOfferBuy.com reasonably believes it is necessary to do so to protect BestOfferBuy.com, its customers, or the public.

 **You can opt-out of BestOfferBuy.com's advertising and marketing list at any time**

Periodically, we may send you information about our various products and services, or other products and services we feel may be of interest to you. Only BestOfferBuy.com will send you these direct mailings. If you do not want to be included on BestOfferBuy.com's advertising and marketing list, simply tell us when you give us your personal information. Or, at any time you can easily opt-out of, or update your information on, BestOfferBuy.com's advertising and marketing list by clicking here.

BestOfferBuy.com will not disclose your personal information to any outside organization for its use in marketing without your consent

Information regarding you (such as name, address and phone number) or your order and the products you purchase will not be given or sold to any outside organization for its use in marketing or solicitation without your consent. 

**Internet Commerce**

The online store at BestOfferBuy.com is designed to give you options concerning the privacy of your credit card information, name, address, e-mail and any other information you provide us. BestOfferBuy.com is committed to data security with respect to information collected on our site. We offer the industry standard security measures available through your browser called SSL encryption. If at any time you would like to make a purchase, but do not want to provide your credit card information online, you may contact a sales representative over the telephone. It has always been a BestOfferBuy.com practice to contact customers in the event of a potential problem with your purchase or any normal business communication regarding your purchase.

 **Customized Experience**

New technologies are emerging on the Internet that help us deliver customized visitor experiences. At BestOfferBuy.com, we primarily use "cookies" to help us determine which service and support information is appropriate to your machine and to maintain your shopping experience in our online store. Our use of this technology does not mean that we automatically know any information about you. We might be able to ascertain what type of computer you are using, but beyond that, our use of cookies is designed only to provide you with a better experience when using [www.BestOfferBuy.com](http://www.bestofferbuy.com/). BestOfferBuy.com has no desire or intent to infringe on your privacy while using the BestOfferBuy.com site. 

**Privacy Statement Effective Date: Dec 01, 2007  
**
